(Raj:)Okay.
See? People get it.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHATTERING]
(Raj:)Mm. By Odin's beard,
this is good Chex Mix.
(Howard:)No, thanks. Peanuts.
(Howard:)I can't afford to swell up in these tights.
(Sheldon:)I'm confused.
(Sheldon:)If there's no costume parade,
what are we doing here?
We're socializing, meeting new people.
(Sheldon:)Telepathically?
- Oh, hey. When did you get here?
WOMAN: Hi.
(Raj:)Penny is wearing the worst
Catwoman costume I've ever seen.
(Raj:)And that includes Halle Berry's.
(Leonard:)She's not Catwoman.
She's just a generic cat.
(Sheldon:)And that's the kind
of sloppy costuming...
(Sheldon:)...which results
from a lack of rules and competition.
(Howard:)Hey, guys, check out the sexy nurse.